Nana Ama Konadu Aning

Project Management and Administration

Professional Summary

A versatile professional with Administration, Project Management, Office Management, and Executive Assistant experience, known for successfully executing diverse administrative and project tasks to accomplish pending deadlines. An enthusiastic problem solver and talented performer with superior communication, planning, organizing, and decision-making skills.

Work Experience

Student "O-Leaders" - Move-in Helpers (Part-Time)

Cambrian College of Arts and Technology, Sudbury, Canada September 2022 -July 2024

Project Management and Business Development Consultant

9K Media Hub, Accra, Ghana, September 2022 - July 2024

- Successfully led and managed projects from initiation to completion, ensuring strict adherence to project scope, timelines, and budgets.
- Developed and implemented strategies to identify and pursue new business opportunities.
- Conducted regular project reviews to assess quality, identify areas for improvement, and ensure compliance with industry standards.

Project Manager / Administrator

Hospital Engineering Limited, Accra, Ghana, June 2020 - April 2024

- Led project planning, execution, and delivery on schedule and within budget.
- Oversaw procurement activities and ensured the availability and proper allocation of resources.
- Reported and escalated to upper management and key stakeholders as needed.
- Performed reconciliation of project costs with the general ledger.
- Prepared and presented progress reports to key stakeholders.
- Assessed project performance using appropriate project management tools.

Office Manager / Administrator / Executive Assistant to Managing Director

Hospital Engineering Limited, Accra, Ghana, July 2019 - May 2020

- Prepared corporate-level administrative expense budgets.
- Managed 20 employees to maximize productivity while training new staff.
- Optimized workflow processes, assessed daily productivity, and made changes to boost staff activity efficiency.
- Coordinated and sourced vendors for special project needs and negotiated contracts.
- Oversaw office inventory activities, including ordering and requisitions, stocking, and shipment receiving.

Office Manager/Administrator

Licensed Stevedore Operators Association, Tema Port, Ghana, December 2015 - July 2019

Established and maintained office operations, procedures, and administrative and

Contact

Phone: +1 (249) 979-5677

Email: nana.konadugh@yahoo.com

Location: Sudbury, Ontario, Canada

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/nana-amakonadu-aning-8000b971/

Skills

Professional

- **Project Management**
- **Effective Communication**
- Administrative Coordination and Team Support
- Planning and Organizing
- Report Analysis & Problem Solving
- Attention to detail & Confidentiality

Technical

Microsoft Office

Project Management Software and Digital tools

Education

MSc Engineering Project Management

Coventry University, United Kingdom September/2020 - July/2022 Graduated with distinction

Post Graduate Certificate in Business Analytics

Cambrian College of Arts and Technology, Canada

May 2024 - Date

BA in Economics and Statistics

University of Ghana, Accra, Ghana September/2011 - May/2015

Languages

English

Native

Nana Ama Konadu Aning

Project Management and Administration

data management systems.

• Developed and implemented computer and physical filing systems.

Google Project Management: Professional Certificate

- Oversaw procurement activities, including ordering and requisitions, stocking, and shipment receiving.
- Optimized organizational systems for payment collections, AP/AR, deposits, and recordkeeping.
- · Managed budgets, appointment and meeting scheduling, event itineraries, and accounts to improve productivity initiatives.

Licenses and Certifications

2023

	Credential ID: PVNU749UDNMK
2022	Lean Six Sigma White Belt, MF Treinamentos, Brazil Credential ID: JLHFDRHRHK-BTZTQQCN-YDSWRGWWGB
2020	Professional Development in Data Analytics for Decision Making: An Introduction to Using Excel, Bond University, Australia
2017	Professional Development in Developing Your Research Project, University of Southampton, Southampton, United Kingdom
2015	Professional Development in Ghana Stock Exchange Securities Course, Ghana Investment and Securities Institute, Accra, Ghana
	Credential ID: GSE/15/108981

Trainings, Conferences, and Workshops

2023	Delegation Trip to Germany for Strengthening the Physical and Digital Infrastructure of Ghana's Healthcare Sector
2022	Delegation Trip to Germany for Strengthening the Physical and Digital Infrastructure of Ghana's Healthcare Sector
2020	Arab Health Conference 2020, Dubai, United Arab Emirates (UAE)
2019	Record Management Training, Public Records and Archives Administration Department (PRAAD), Accra, Ghana
2018	Monitoring and Evaluation Training, African Evaluation Association (AFrEA), Accra, Ghana

Projects

Date from - Date to	Location(s)	Company / Project Partners	Position	Project Name
2023-Now	Accra	Hospital Engineering / German Development Cooperation (GIZ) in collaboration with Ghana Health Service	Project Coordinator	Ghana Heart Initiative (GHI) Ihre Bestell Project Nr. 7500083340/Ghana
2023	9 Regions in Ghana	9K Media Hub / Bliss GVS Pharma	Project Manager	PR activation project (ACT for Africa Campaign) for World Malaria Day 2023
2022-2023	Accra Kumasi Tamale Cape Coast	Hospital Engineering & African German Health Association (AGHA) / German Development Cooperation (GIZ) in collaboration with the Ministry of Health & Ghana Health Service	Project Manager	Strengthening Together the Physical and Digital Infrastructure of Ghana's Healthcare Sector Project (Coalition for Health – C4H), Ghana
2022	Accra	Hospital Engineering / German Development Cooperation (GIZ) in collaboration with the Ministry of Health & Ghana Health Service	Project Manager	Covid-19 Vaccination Campaign Training and Workshop Programme, Ghana

Nana Ama Konadu Aning

Project Management and Administration

2021-2022	Komfo Anokye Teaching Hospital (KATH), Kumasi	Hospital Engineering / German Development Cooperation (GIZ) in collaboration with the Ministry of Health	Project Coordinator	"GIZ-Covid-19" Project Nr 81264009, Ghana
2021-2022	Accra Kumasi Saltpond	Hospital Engineering & African German Health Association (AGHA) / German Development Cooperation (GIZ) in collaboration with the Ministry of Health & Ghana Health Service	Project Coordinator	Strengthening Together the Physical and Digital Infrastructure of Ghana's Healthcare Sector Project (Coalition for Health – C4H), Ghana
2020-2022	Accra	Hospital Engineering / German Development Cooperation (GIZ) in collaboration with the Ministry of Health & Ghana Health Service	Project Coordinator	COVID-19 – Alliance of Ghanaian Hospitals to Secure Medical Staff Project, Ghana

Project Media Publications:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TRWLsg9u0wQ

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qvLpHRdyvIs

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nryWm_fRW3k

https://www.ghanaiantimes.com.gh/bliss-gvs-pharma-presents-gh%E2%82%B5150000-anti-malaria-drugs-to-hospitals/

https://citinewsroom.com/2023/04/ho-hospital-receives-antimalaria-drugs-from-bliss-gvs-pharma-ghana/

https://www.ghanaiantimes.com.gh/e2m-covid-19-vaccination-uptake-campaign-launched/

https://www.graphic.com.gh/news/general-news/giz-partners-ghana-health-service-to-improve-covid-19-vaccination-uptake.html

https://citinewsroom.com/2022/10/agha-and-giz-organize-covid-19-vaccination-campaign/

https://www.myjoyonline.com/agha-partners-giz-ghs-to-organise-covid-19-workshop-for-healthcare-service-providers/

https://www.ghanaiantimes.com.gh/over-21-1m-covid-19-vaccines-administered-nationwide/

https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/National-COVID-19-vaccine-sensitization-campaign-yields-results-1673108

Community Engagements and Volunteering Activities:

Volunteer Coordinator, Summer Fun Fest

Cambrian College, Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, July 2024

I collaborated with event organizers to execute a successful fundraising event.

Volunteer at Open House Event

Cambrian College, Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, June 2024

• I assisted guests with their questions and concerns and directed them to various campus areas.

Volunteer with MS Canada for MS Walk

MS Canada, Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, May 2024

• I assisted in setting up the event venue, collaborated on logistics, including registration booths and water stations, and supported participants with registration and queries to ensure a welcoming atmosphere.